雪音くん　いる
クッキー焼いたんだ
ココアとここに置いておくね
Yukine-kun? Are you there?
I baked some cookies.
I'll leave them here with
some hot chocolate, okay?
雪音くん
Yukine-kun?
弾丸込めた小銃を　僕は片手に持っている
震えた君のいる場所へ　足を早め向かっている
Noragami
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
焦る心を急かしただけ
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
留まる気配もなく　進んでいく
チクタク　針はチクタクと
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
チクタク　針はチクタクと
終わりと始まりの境目
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
終わりと始まりの境目
チクタク　針はチクタクと
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
チクタク　針はチクタクと
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
全て重なった
閉口して　僕は待っていた
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
owari to hajimari no sakaime
閉口して　僕は待っていた
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
閉口して　僕は待っていた
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
ドアを蹴破る　その音を
閉口して　僕は待っていた
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
閉口して　僕は待っていた
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
閉口して　僕は待っていた
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
閉口して　僕は待っていた
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
閉口して　僕は待っていた
もう怖れることはないよ
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
もう怖れることはないよ
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
弾丸込めた小銃を持って
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
弾丸込めた小銃を持って
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
固く閉ざされたドアを蹴破った
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
吸い付いた銃口が跳ねて
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
昨日の僕を貫いた
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
おやすみ　その絶望を受け取って
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
おやすみ　その絶望を受け取って
dan
gan
ko
me
ta
sho
u
ju
wo
mo
明日への僕は歩き始めた
tte
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
明日への僕は歩き始めた
ka
ta
ku
to
za
sa
re
ta
do
a
wo
ke
ya
bu
tta
また今夜　待ち合わせよう
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
また今夜　待ち合わせよう
su
i
また今夜　待ち合わせよう
tsu
i
ta
ju
u
ko
ga
ha
ne
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
ki
no
u
bo
ku
wo
tsu
ra
nu
i
ta
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
ma
ta
ko
n'
ya
ma
chi
a
wa
se
you
Let's meet again tonight
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作，仅供交流学习，禁止用于任何商业用途
日听:小然&千夜  翻译:maki&迩祢  校对:木落&叶隐  时间轴:Gissa  压制:久嘉
くそ
Damn it.
一線
Borderline!
Why am I acting so paranoid?
何ビビってんだよ　俺
夜トが俺を無理やり使ったからだ
This is Yato's fault for using me against my will.
止めろ
Stop!
Rend!
斬
That's no different from stealing!
それじゃ　泥棒と一緒だよ
Damn it!
くそ
God damn it! Hiyori, too!
くそ　何だよ　ひよりも
What the...
何だ
あいつ
That kid...
Chapter 6
Scary Person
Not here either...
ここにもいない
雪音くん　あれからずっと塞いでた
Yukine-kun's been acting really depressed since that night,
夜トも呼びに来ないし
and Yato hasn't come for him.
あんなショックなことがあった後じゃ　無理も無いよね
Considering what happened,
I can't really blame him.
Oh! Hiyori-chan!
あれ　ひよりじゃん
あみちゃん　やまちゃん
Ami-chan! Yama-chan!
I know it's a day off, but should you really be wandering around instead of studying?
休日とはいえ　ほっつき歩いてていいのか　受験生
What about you? You guys have to take entrance exams, too.
それは二人も一緒でしょう
ひよりは授業中寝てばっかだもんね
Yeah, but you're always asleep during class.
高校進学っつっても　うちらはクラスごと繰り上がるけど
Usually, the whole class gets to move on to the next grade...
稀にバカは落ちるからな
...but some fools do get held back, you know.
ちゃんと家でも勉強してます
For your information,
I do study when I'm at home.
そうだ
Say, have either of you
seen a boy wearing a parka?
二人ども モッズコート着た男の子見なかった
He's about this tall.
これぐらいの背の
A boy?
男
Yeah! He's pretty young, too.
うん　男の子
Operative
Mrs. Iki! I'm afraid your daughter has been caught in an illicit relationship!
壱岐の伯母様　娘さんに虫がついてますよ
Operative
She's messing around in
the middle of exam season!
Operative
受験前に浮ついてますよ　こいつ
No! Mother! It's not like that!
It's a misunderstanding!
Operative
お母様　誤解です　誤解
You seem to have a thing for ugly guys, too!
Operative
ひよりはぶっせんだからな
どうせブサ男だろ
Operative
I bet he's all gross-looking!
Touno
The Ultimate Wimp!
Just look at your beloved Touno after he lost!
見ろよ　お前の蟷野の負け面
Operative
Touno
The Ultimate Wimp!
Operative
やめて　今晩録画見るつもりだったのに
Stop! I was gonna watch
my recording of that tonight!
今度彼氏紹介してね
Introduce us to your boyfriend sometime!
蟷野みたいなの期待してんぞ
He'd better look like Touno!
だから違うのに
Seriously, it's not like that!
Man, that girl needs some divine intervention.
くそ　かくなる上は神頼みだなあ
I would like to introduce them to Yato and Yukine-kun some day.
いつか二人にも　夜トや雪音くんを紹介したいな
Though they'd probably
forget about them right away.
でも
紹介しても　やまちゃんたちはすぐに忘れちゃうかもしれない
Plus...
それに
私も　夜トのこと　よく知らない
I don't even know Yato that well myself.
Man! That was easy!
なんだ　ちょろいじゃん
I can pretty much do whatever I want!
これだったら　何でも
What the hell, man?!
何すんだよ
Yato!
夜ト
Where'd you get this?
これ　どうした
H-Hiyori bought it for me.
ひよりに買ってもらったんだよ
Really?
Yukine-kun!
雪音くん
Thank goodness! So you were with Yato!
良かった　夜トと一緒だったんですね
Hiyori, I hear you bought this for him.
ひより　これお前が買ってやったんだって
Y-Yeah, that's right!
そう　買ってあげたよ
I bought it for him!
Man, this is why I can't stand kids.
ったく　これだからガキは
The sky's a nice shade of crimson right now.
見事な茜色だな
Twilight acts as the boundary
between day and night.
黄昏は昼と夜の境目
Those that inhabit this world fear the darkness and hide from it...
現世の者は闇を恐れ　身を潜め
...while those that inhabit the other world
become one with the darkness and run wild.
常世の者は闇に紛れて　跋扈する
暮の日は　すべてを赤に染めあげ　あやふやにし
As the sun sets, that boundary is blurred...
宵の影は　より深く濃い物となる
...and the shadows of evening grow ever deeper and darker.
この時分　狭間にいるものたちは　境界を越えやすい
Those that exist in the divide can
easily cross the boundary at this time.
People once said this is the time of the day when monsters come out.
かつての人は　その時間を魔物と会う時と言った
Yukine.
雪音
お前が今いるのは
This is now...
逢魔が時
...the Fiends' Hour.
い　痛ぇ
Ow...
Wh—
や
しっ
Wh-What's going on?!
何
言葉にするもんじゃねえな
Well, speak of the devil.
Looks like we're in serious trouble now.
マジでおっかない奴に遭っちまった
見つけたぞ　禍津神
I've found you, god of calamity.
Bishamon...
毘沙門
Bishamon?!
Yeah. The strongest war god I know.
ああ　俺が知りうる最強の武神だ
A god? Isn't she on your side, then?!
神様　それで仲間じゃねえのかよ
What's she attacking us for?!
何でこんな
昔あの女と揉めた
I sort of got on her bad side a while back.
She's been out to kill me ever since.
以来あいつに命を狙われてる
Huh?!
俺　いち抜けた
Well then, I want no part of this! You can deal with her yourself!
夜トだけで相手しなよ
I'm not sure she's just gonna let you walk away.
さて　あの女がお前だけ見逃すかな
あの女の狙いは復讐だ
She wants revenge.
なら　神器ごと斬るはず
I'm sure she wants to take
me and my Regalia out.
No way!
何だよ　それ
It may be a grudge that drives me to slay you,
貴様らを討つは私怨なれど
but regardless, it is my duty
to bring justice to all evil!
邪悪を誅するは世の理
Come, Sekki!
来い　雪器
Wa—
待っ
You won't escape!
逃すまいぞ
B-Bishamon? As in the god
that punishes sinners?!
毘沙門って　あの毘沙門天のこと
夜トに復讐
Revenge against Yato?
Slaying him and his Regalia?
神器ごと　斬る
もし　俺に何かあったら
If anything happens to me,
go straight to those two.
あの二人の所に行け
Track him, Kazuma.
追尾を頼む　カズマ
Understood.
了解
Target traveling northeast.
目標は北北東に直進中
Distance: 2.1.
距離 2.1　1.9
1.9.
There aren't many Near Shore denizens in the area, but you should still limit the scale of your attacks.
此岸の人は疎らですが
攻撃範囲は極力抑えてください
One Regalia. Abilities unknown.
神器は一体の模様
能力は不明です
Slashing is the only thing
he's decent at, anyway.
どうせ斬るしか能のない男だ
Pincer attack, Kuraha!
挟み撃ちにするぞ　クラハ
You got it, milady!
任せな　お嬢
I will end this today!
今日で終わりにしてやる
What are you doing?! Hurry!
何してんだ　急げよ
Before she catches us!
追いつかれるぞ
うるせー
Oh, shut up. It's partly
your fault I'm so tired now!
無駄に疲れんのは　お前のせいでもあんだぞ
Huh?!
Quit acting like such a baby.
ビビッてんじゃねえよ
別にビビッてなんか
I-I'm not acting like...
分んだよ
I can tell!
この間から　ぐさぐさ刺しあがって
I've been getting pricked nonstop!
Your emotional state affects me too, you know!
いいか　お前の精神状態は俺に影響すんの
覚えとけ
Get that through your head!
だってあの人　同じ神様なんだろ
But she's a god, just like you.
Are you seriously gonna fight against a god?!
夜ト　神様と戦う気かよ
仕掛けて来てんのはあっちだ
She's the one attacking us.
Are you... going to use me to kill her?
俺で　斬るのかよ
当たり前だ
Of course!
You are my Regalia!
お前は俺の神器だろ
Everything she has with her—
those weapons, clothes, and that beast—
毘沙門が身につけているものは
武器や服
従わせてる獣にいたるまで　全てが神器だ
is a Regalia.
あのライオンも神器
Even that lion's a Regalia?!
Yeah.
ああ
特にナビのカズマは秀逸で
Her navigator, Kazuma, is particularly skilled.
He coordinates the other Regalia,
すべての神器を取りまとめ
毘沙門を最高の武神たらしめる 道標だ
and his guidance is what makes
Bishamon the mightiest war god of all.
Hey! Where are you going?!
She's gonna spot us!
おい　どこへ行くんだ　見つかるぞ
逃げきるのは無理だ
We can't escape her!
体力があるうちに　ここで迎え撃つ
I'm going to take her out here while I still have strength left!
What?! But I don't want to!
俺は嫌だって
It's her!
来た
Noragami
So powerful!
重い
まともに受ければ　雪器が折れる
A clean hit would snap Sekki in two!
Catch him, Kinuha!
捕えろ　キヌハ
It grabbed you! It's a Regalia, too?!
掴んできた　こいつも神器
Yeah!
そうだよ
Now keep quiet for a bit, Yukine!
いいからちょっと黙れ　雪音
ガイキ
Gaiki!
Locking on.
銃口固定
Aiming for cervical vertebrae and left humerus.
頚椎及び左上腕側を打ち抜きます
Zero point in two, one...
ゼロ点到達まで２　１
Fire!
撃て
Impressive.
うまい
Pardon me.
失礼
Kinuha!
キヌハ
貴様
How dare you!
よくも
Never again will I let you kill a Regalia!
貴様に二度と神器は殺させぬ
Huh?!
お前　神器を殺したことが
You've killed a Regalia before—
黙ってろって言ってんだろ　雪音
I told you to shut up, Yukine!
Just leave me alone already,
you half-naked, jacket-wearing tramp!
いい加減 もう俺のことほっとけよ
この痴女
裸ジャケット
何年ストーカーやってる
You've been stalking me for years!
貴様の名すら許しておけぬのだ
Your very name is vulgar!
滅殺するのみ
I must eradicate you!
Suki!
数器
鈍った
It's been dulled?!
Hey! What are you doing, Yukine?!
おい　何やってんだ　雪音
Damn!
くそっ
Kofuku-san!
小福さん
Oh, you need something, Hiyori-chan?
おや　どうした　ひよりちゃん
ひよりん　ちょうどいいところに
Hiyorin! Perfect timing!
Tell us, which kind of daifuku bun do you like better, the kind with—
あのね　大福は粒餡と漉し餡　どっちが
I-It's Yato!
夜トが　毘沙門天に襲われて
Bishamon attacked him!
毘沙門に
Bishamon?
ありゃー　毘沙ったらまた夜トちゃん追い掛け回してるんだ
Oh my! Bisha is still after Yato-chan?
あの　夜ト　毘沙門に禍津神って呼ばれてました
Um, she called Yato a "god of calamity."
禍津神って
What does that mean?
災いを齎す神様のことだよ
A god that causes disaster.
Huh?
I already told you that Yato-chan's
actually a scary war god, remember?
夜トちゃん　本当は怖い武神だって言ったでしょ
Yato-chan killed a Regalia a long time ago.
夜トちゃん　昔神器を斬ったことがあるの
Wait...
まさか
夜トが斬ったのは毘沙門天の神器なんですね
Does that mean it was Bishamon's Regalia that Yato killed?
This is between Yato and Bishamon.
これは夜トと毘沙門の問題だ
俺達はどうこうすることじゃねえ
It's none of our business.
で　でも
B-But Yato told me to come to you for help!
夜トが二人を頼れって
お願い　助けて
Please, help him! Lend him your assistance!
力を貸してください
Why are you so desperate?
どうしてそんなに必死なの
Oh, do you have a thing for Yato-chan?!
もしかしてひよりん 夜トちゃんに
Huh?! N-No, not really!
わ　私は別に
Is he blackmailing you, then?
弱みを握られてんだな
強請られてんの
Extortion?
Wow, no one trusts him at all!
なんて信用のない人なの
いえ　私の体質の件でちょっと
No, it's about what's happened to my body.
大丈夫よ　ひよりん
Don't worry, Hiyorin! I'll help you!
あたしが助けてあげる
小福さん
Kofuku-san!
I'll take your money offering later!
お賽銭は後ででいいからねえ
え？
Huh?
Looks like you got a deal.
Don't come crying to me later.
契約成立か
どうなっても知らねえぞ
So, where is Yato?
で　夜トはどこにいんだよ
I don't know.
分かりません
Wait...
ううん　分かるかも
Maybe I do!
Whoa! She has a Cord!
わ　「緒」がある
半妖か
She's a half-Phantom?
All the gods have a nice smell to them.
神様たちは　一様にいい香りがする
But each one smells slightly different.
でもその香りは微妙に違ってて
That way!
あっちです
夜ト
Yato.
Huh?
Did you really kill that girl's Regalia?
さっきの　あの人の神器
本当に殺したのか
ああ
Yeah.
Then it's only natural that she wants revenge.
それじゃ復讐されて当然だな
Why'd you do it?
何で
Because I wanted to.
斬りたいから斬った
That's all.
そんだけだ
そんなに簡単に斬れるんだ
So it's that easy, huh?
What are you talking about?
何言ってんだ
じゃあ　もし俺がへましたら　斬られるのか
What about me, then?
Will you kill me if I screw up?
俺が必要でなくなったら
If you don't need me more anymore?
Yeah, even without me, Yato still has that Regalia named Nora.
俺がいなくなっても
夜トにはまだあの「野良」って神器があるのか
また刺しやがった
You're pricking me again.
Man, will you just grow a pair already?!
つーか　マジお前勘弁しろよ
Huh?
は？
You've been acting like a real wimp!
先からびびりすぎだろ
おかげでこっちは絶不調だ
I can barely do a thing like this, you pushover!
このへたれ
You hypocrite! You're scared, too!
お前だってびびってるくせに
What?!
手汗いつもの五倍はかいてんぜ
Your hands are five times greasier than usual, you sweatbag!
この手びしょ
Who the hell are you
calling a "sweatbag"?!
手びしょってなんだよこら
うるせえ　そのまんまだよ　バーカ
Who do you think, dipshit?!
Takes a dipshit to know a one!
お前
バカって言うほうがバカなんだぞ
バーカバーカ
You freaking dipshit!
S-Sekki!
せ　雪器
What are you, a walking armory?
「歩く武器庫」かよ
Man, you took out this Near Shore life too.
此岸のものまで斬っちまって
This part of the woods is as good as dead now.
そこらの林　だめになんぞ
邪悪を斬るためだ
I'm willing to overlook some immorality for the sake of purging evil.
多少の不義は構うまい
さすが　その邪悪に生かされただけあんな
I can tell this "evil" is really
bringing out the best of you.
Look at all that tolerance for immorality.
不義に寛容でいらっしゃる
それが遺言か
Are those your last words?
H-Hey! Don't you take that stance!
That thing'll tear right through me!
おい　構うなよ
あんなの受けたら折れちまう
夜トちゃん
Yato-chan!
Found you!
みっけ
Kofuku?!
小福
小福殿
Kofuku-dono?!
Come, Kokki!
おいで　黒器
二人とも　喧嘩は
All right, you two!
That's...
それは
Stop! Are you crazy?!
止せバカ
Stop your fighting!
やめなさい
What just happened?!
何だこれ
風穴を開けやがった
She blasted open a Vent!
That's why I told her to stop!
だから止せって言ったんだ
小福が黒器を使うと　一気に時化る
Kofuku causes sudden Storms whenever she uses Kokki!
Phantoms are gushing out
from the underworld!
黄泉からあやかしが溢れてきています
Bishamon-sama! I suggest we retreat!
毘沙門さま　ここは一旦
Don't falter!
怯むな
クラハ
Kuraha!
Yato!
夜ト
Kuraha.
クラハ
Restraint.
縛布
Kinki!
ケンキ
Kazuma! Tend to Kuraha!
カズマ　クラハを頼む
How dare you!
貴様
毘沙門様　ここは一旦退きましょう
Bishamon-sama, we should retreat for now.
敵は　やつは目の前だ
Our archenemy's standing right there!
A mere Vent won't keep me from my enemy!
風穴ごときで
Veena!
ヴィーナ
あなた一人があやかしに食われたいならどうぞご自由に
If you wish to be food for the Phantoms,
please go right ahead.
ただ　手傷を負ったクラハらにもそれを強いられるのか
But can you really force the same upon the injured Kuraha and the others?!
ちっ
何これは　何事
What?! What is this?!
ひよりだな　あいつら呼んだのは
Hiyori! You sent them here?!
You told me to go to them if anything happened to you!
だって夜トに何かあったらあの二人にって
Oh... I didn't mean for this to happen!
それは今じゃねえ
毘沙門に遭遇したのは想定外だったんだ
I never expected I'd run into Bishamon!
Oh, no!
大変
Anyway, you need to hide!
それよりお前　隠れてろ
Huh?
And don't call my name.
俺の名も呼ぶな
We can't risk Bishamon finding out you're connected to me!
縁があると毘沙門に知られたらやっかいだ
Right!
はい
小福殿に免じて今日のところは見逃してやる
Out of consideration for Kofuku-dono, I'll let you go for today.
次は必ず殺してやる
But I will kill you next time.
With my own two hands!
私の手で
Don't taint yourself any further.
それ以上やすむなよ
行くぞ　カズマ
Let's go, Kazuma!
ひよりちゃん
Hiyori-chan!
It's dangerous here!
You need to get out of here, too!
君も逃げろ　あぶねえぞ
R-Right!
はい
やってくれたな　小福
You really did it this time, Kofuku!
あたしすごい
Are you impressed?
お前のせいで最悪だって言ってんだ　バーカ
I'm saying you screwed everything up, you dolt!
てめえ　うちのかみさんに助けてもらったくせに
You ingrate! My lady saved your sorry ass!
Ow! That hurt, Daikoku!
いてえ　いてえよ　大黒
うるせえ
I heard that the wind really
picked up in the city around sunset.
夕方街中で突風が吹いてたらしいのよ
ご近所の林の木も薙ぎ倒されたんですって
Some nearby woods were
completely knocked down.
怖いわ
How frightening.
It's no good. I can't cleanse it all.
だめだ
清めきれない
Yukine... Is this just not
gonna work between us?
雪音　お前じゃだめなのか
Don't look so down, Yato.
夜ト　そんな顔しないで
You can always use me, you know.
あたしを使えばいいのに
Nora...
野良
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
ki
mi
no
na
ma
e
na
ni
ga
a
tte
mo
ka
na
ra
zu
yo
bu
ka
ra
君の名前 何があっても
必ず呼ぶから
Your heart is all jagged
ki
mi
wa
gi
za
ha
a
to
no
mo
chi
nu
shi
君はぎざぎざハートの持ち主
So you hurt anything you touch
fu
re
ru
mo
no
wa
na
n
de
mo
ki
zu
tsu
ke
ru
触れるものは何でも傷つけ
Those eyes that frown at everything
se
ka
i
no
su
be
te
wo
ni
ra
mi
tsu
ke
te
世界のすべてを睨み付けて
その目は言うんだ
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
so
no
me
wa
i
un
da
bo
ku
wa
ko
ni
iru
「僕はここにいる」
Someone was laughing at you
da
re
ka
ga
wa
ra
tte
ta
誰かが笑ってた
だから引いたんだ その境界線
So you put that barrier around you
da
ka
ra
hi
i
tan
da
so
no
kyo
u
ka
i
sen
But I'll reach in there with my hand
so
re
na
ra
wa
ta
shi
ga
so
no
te
wo
hi
ku
それなら
私はその手を引く
さぁ
And bring you out
tsu
re
te
ku
ka
ra
連れてくから
言えないなら
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
i
e
na
i
ra
ko
no
te
wo
tsu
yo
ku
ni
gi
tte
この手を強く握って
And don't let go
ha
na
sa
i
de
離さないで
君はもう一人じゃないんだって
I want you to know that you
ki
mi
wa
mo
u
hi
to
ri
ja
na
i
n
da
tte
知ってほしいんだよ
Are not alone any more
shi
tte
ho
shi
in
da
yo
見事な茜色だな
The sky's a nice shade of crimson right now.
ひより　茜色ってのはな
Hiyori. "Crimson" is—
"Crimson" originally referred to the color of a dye made from Kermes vermilio, right?
アカネ科の蔓性多年草茜草の根で染めた色のことですよね
あっ　うん　そう
Uh, right.
On the next Noragami: "Uncertainty & Destiny."
次回　ノラガミ
迷い事　定め事
ひより物知りだな
You sure know a lot, Hiyori.
&
Uncertainty
Destiny
Next Episode
一応受験生ですから
This is exam season, after all!